Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Subjects PE.029
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- L, 1878-2018; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 3 manuscript boxes
  - Labor Management Relations Act / Taft-Hartley Bill, 1947- (Box 7)
  - Labor Movement, 1922-2011 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  - Labor Poetry, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Landlord and Tenant, 1970- (Box 7)
  - Laos, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Latin America, 1965- (Box 7)
  - Laundry Industry, 1922-1946 (Box 7)
  - Lebanon, 1981 (Box 7, Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Leftism, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Leninism, 1934-1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Libertarianism, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Libraries, 1971-2007 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Libya: Labor Situation in, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Liquor Traffic Issues: Labor Unions, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Literature, 1878-1970 (Box 39, Folder 9, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Lobbying, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Longshoremen, 1958-2004 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Lower East Side, 1965-1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Louisville Pattern Investigation, 1954- (Box 7)
  - Loyalty Oaths, undated (Box 7)
  - Loyalty-Security Program, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Ludlow Massacre (CO) 1914, 1997-, undated (Box 8)
  - Lynching, 1948-1949 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- M, 1911-2006; 3.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, and 1 flat file folder
  - Manchuria, undated (Box 8)
  - Maoism: Great Britain, 1972- (Box 8)
  - Maoism: U.S. I, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Maoism: U.S. II, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Maps, undated (Flat-file-folder TBD, Folder TBD, Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Maquiladoras, 1995- (Box 8)
  - Marajuana, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6, Box 40, Folder 7)
  - March for Racial Justice, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Maritime Workers, 2003-2006 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Marriage, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Marshall Plan, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Marxism, 1921-1978 (Box 8, Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Maternity League, 1990 (Box 8)
  - May Day I, 1918-1963 (Box 8, Box 40, Folder 13)
  - May Day II, 1918-, undated (Box 8)
  - May Day: Great Britain, 1931 (Box 8)
  - May Day: Washington, D.C., 1971 (Box 8)
  - McCarran Act - Immigration bill, 1962 (Box 8)
  - McCarthy, Eugene (Presidential candidate), 1968 (Box 8)
  - McCarthyism, 1953, undated (Box 8, Box 40, Folder 14)
  - McGovern-Shriver Campaign, 1972 (Box 8)
  - McNamara Defense Fund Committee, 1911 (Box 8)
  - Media, 1989- (Box 8)
  - Medicine: Socialized, 1939- (Box 8)
  - Men's Liberation Movement, undated (Box 8)
  - Mexico -- Indigenous Peoples, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Middle East, 1969-1985 (Box 8, Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Middle East: Persian Gulf Crisis / Gulf War I, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Middle East: Persian Gulf Crisis / Gulf War II, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Migrant Labor, 1939-1976 (Box 8)
  - Migrant Labor, 1949-1981, undated (Box 8)
  - Militarism, undated (Box 8)
  - Military Contractors, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Military prisons, 1918- (Box 8)
  - Military Recruiters on College Campuses, 1969-2003 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Military Service, Compulsory, 1926- (Box 8)
  - Military Spending, 1957-1986 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Miners, 1912-1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Milk, 1949- (Box 8)
  - Million Worker March, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Milwaukee 14, undated (Box 8)
  - Minimum Wage / Living Wage, 1939- (Box 8)
  - Minneapolis "Sedition" Trial, 1941 (Box 9)
  - "Mission to Moscow" (film; Soviet trials 1930s), undated (Box 9)
  - Mississippi, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Molly Maguires, circa 1978 (Box 9)
  - Moore, Harry T. -- Assassination, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Moral Re-armament, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Moscow Trials, 1938-1945 (Box 9, Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Mozambique, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Mundt-Ferguson Bill (Subversive Activities Control Bill), 1948 (Box 9)
  - Municipal Ownership, 1914 (Box 9)
  - Muscle Shoals, AL - power plant, 1924- (Box 9)
  - Mutualism, undated (Box 9)
  - Music, 1925-1992 (Box 9, Box 41, Folder 4)
- N, 1940-2015; 1.75 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 1 manuscript box, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 shared box
  - Namibia, 1975-1982 (Box 9, Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Nathan Report "National Wage Policy for 1947", 1946 (Box 9)
  - National Healthcare, 1971-, undated (Box 9)
  - National Steel and Shipbuiling Company - Nassco Case, 1981 (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970 (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: New York City I (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: New York City II (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: New York City - Columbia University (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: New York City - New York University I (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: New York City - New York University II (Box 9)
  - National Student Strike, May 1970: Upstate New York (Box 9)
  - National Youth Festival, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Native Americans, 1970-1990 (Box 28, Folder 7, Box 41)
  - Neocolonialism, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - New Right, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - New York World's Fair, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - New Bethel Incident (Detroit), 1969 (Box 9)
  - New Deal, 1933-1939, 1978, undated (Box 9)
  - New Left, History of (paper), 1965-1969, undated (Box 9)
  - New York City: Fiscal Crisis 1975-76 (Box 9)
  - New York City Unemployed Council, 1975 (Box 9)
  - New Zealand, 1948- (Box 9)
  - Nicaragua I, 1975-1991 (Box 9, Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Nicaragua II, 1979-, undated (Box 9)
  - Non-Violence, 1968-2015 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1992-2003 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - North Korea, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Northern Ireland, 1970-1988 (Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 20, Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Norway, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear Arms Race / Disarmament, 1960- (Box 9)
  - Nuclear War - Anti, 1964- (Box 9)
  - Nuclear Weapons - Anti (Box 9)
  - Nuclear Weapons / Disarmament, 1988- (Box 9)
- O, 1920-2016; 6.5 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 shared box
  - Occupational Safety and Health, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Occupational Safety and Health, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Occupational Safety and Health, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Occupy Wall Street, 2011-2016 (Box 24, Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box Shared Tamiment 165, Folder 19)
  - Office Workers, 1920-1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Open and Closed Shop, 1939- (Box 10)
  - Operation Abolition (HUAC), 1961- (Box 10)
  - Oral History, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Organizing, 1939-1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- P, 1871-2014; 5.75 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 shared box
  - Pacifism, 1956- (Box 10)
  - Pakistan, 1961- (Box 10)
  - Pakistan 1964 (Box 10)
  - Palestine I, 1948-2007 (Box 10, Box 28, Folder 11, Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Palestine II, 1948- (Box 10)
  - Palestine III, 1971-2007 (Box 10)
  - Pamphlets, 1911-1944 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Pan-African Movement, 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Pan-African Cultural Festival: Algiers, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Panama, 1973-1992, undated (Box 10)
  - Paris Commune 1871 (Box 10, Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Patients, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Patriot Act, 2003 (Box 10, Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Peace I, 1960-2001 (Box 10, Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Peace II, 1960- (Box 10)
  - Peace III, 1960- (Box 10)
  - Peace (N.J. Peace Action; Peace Action of New York State), 2002-, undated (Box 10)
  - Peace Movement: U.S. - June 12, 1982 Demonstration, Jun 12, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Peekskill (N.Y.), 1949-1950 (Box 10)
  - People's Park: Berkeley 1969 (Box 11)
  - Pentagon Papers, circa 1970s (Box 11)
  - Perestroika, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Philippines I, 1970-1988 (Box 11, Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Philippines I, 1979- (Box 11)
  - Philippines: Pamphlets, 1901-1971 (Box 11)
  - Philosophy, 1941-1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Photography, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Pillion Resolution: H. J. Res. 447, U.S. House of Rep. June 12, 1961 (anti-communism), Jun 12, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Plant Closings, 1979-1982 (Box 11)
  - PM (Progressive Newspaper of New York City), 1940-1948, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Poetry, 1912-2004 (Box 11, Box 43, Folder 5-6)
  - Poland, 1934- (Box 11)
  - Poland, 1942-1949 (Box 11)
  - Poland: Pamphlets I, 1941- (Box 11)
  - Poland: Pamphlets II, 1941- (Box 11)
  - Poletown Lives! (film re: General Motors), 1983 (Box 11)
  - Police / Police Brutality, 1916-2006 (Box 11, Box 28, Folder 12, Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 1)
  - Police Officers: Race Relations (Pamphlets), 1946, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Political Campaigns: U.S., 1950s- (Box 11)
  - Political Campaigns: U.S., 1950s-, undated (Box 11)
  - Political Campaigns and Political Parties (New York), 1953- (Box 11)
  - Political Crimes and Offenses, 1971- (Box 11)
  - Political Crimes and Offenses: Northern Ireland, 1981-1985 (Box 11)
  - Political Crimes and Offenses: Russia/USSR, 1964, undated (Box 11)
  - Political Parties: Maryland, undated (Box 11)
  - Political Parties and Platforms (U.S.), 1908- (Box 11)
  - Political Prisoners I, 1967-2004 (Box 11, Box 28, Folder 13, Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Political Prisoners II, 1972-, undated (Box 11)
  - Poll Tax, 1945- (Box 11)
  - Ponce Massacre, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Population Control, 1970- (Box 11)
  - Portugal, 1935-1970 (Box 11, Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Postcards: Books, Exhibits, Events; various organizations and topics, 1940s, circa 2000- (Box 11)
  - Poujade Movement, undated (Box 12)
  - Poverty I, undated (Box 12, Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Poverty II, 1963- (Box 12)
  - Prisons, 2002, undated (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons I, 1926-2002 (Box 12, Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Prisoners and Prisons II, undated (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons III (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons IV (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons V (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons VI (Box 12)
  - Prisoners and Prisons VII (Box 12)
  - Productivity, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Prohibition, 1888- (Box 12)
  - Proletariat, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Propaganda, 1958-2011 (Box 12, Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Proportional Representation, 1913- (Box 12)
  - Prussia (Germany), 1908 (Box 12)
  - Public Ownership of Utilities, undated (Box 12)
  - Puerto Ricans in New York, 1954- (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico I, 1947-2014 (Box 12, Box 28, Folder 14, Box 44, Folder 8-9)
  - Puerto Rico II, 1957- (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico: Pamphlets I, 1945- (Box 12)
  - Puerto Rico: Pamphlets II, 1945- (Box 13)
  - Puerto Rico: Pamphlets III, 1945- (Box 13)
  - Pullman, IL (Pullman Workers), 1884-2003 (Box 13)
  - Pullman Porters, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Q, 1963; 0.1 Linear Feet in 1 folder
  - Quebec-Washington-Guantanamo Walk for Peace, 1963 (Box 13)
- R, 1900-2004; 5.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 5 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize flat box
  - Race Relations and Racism I, 1956-2004 (Box 13, Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Race Relations and Racism II, 1965- (Box 13)
  - Radicalism, undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Red International of Labor Unions (Profintern) -- Fourth World Conference, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Riots -- Detroit and Newark, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Riots -- Rodney King Trial, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Railroads, 1914-1927 (Box 13, Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Rank and File Activitiy, 1968-1971, undated (Box 13)
  - Reaganism, 1981-1983 (Box 45, Folder 2, Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Red Diaper Babies, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Red Flag (Socialism), 1975, undated (Box 13)
  - Refugees, 2000, undated (Box 13)
  - Regicide, 1900 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Religion, 1933-1988 (Box 28, Folder 15, Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Religion and Labor, 1943- (Box 13)
  - Rent Control: New York City, 1963, undated (Box 13)
  - Reparations, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Representation, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights I, 1971- (Box 13)
  - Reproductive Rights II, 1971- (Box 13)
  - Reproductive Rights III, 1971- (Box 13)
  - Republican National Convention, 2004, undated (Box 13)
  - Retirement, 1959- (Box 13)
  - Revisionism, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Revolutions, 1907, undated (Box 28, Folder 16, Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Revolutions -- Africa, 1963-1977 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Revolutions -- India, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Right to Work I, 1950- (Box 13)
  - Right to Work II, 1950- (Box 13)
  - Right Wing I, 1960- (Box 13)
  - Right Wing II, 1960- (Box 13)
  - Right Wing: Pamphlets, 1938-1965 (Box 13)
  - Right Wing: Periodicals I, 1967-1972 (Box 14)
  - Right Wing: Periodicals II, 1967-1972 (Box 14)
  - Romania / Rumania, 1946- (Box 14)
  - Rosenberg-Sobell Case, 1952-1957 (Box 14, Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Rosie the Riveter, 1982, undated (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR), 1912-1982 (Box 14, Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Russia (1923- USSR), 1958- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923-USSR), 1967- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Army, undated (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Constitutions, 1919- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Constitutions, 1924-1958, undated (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Culture I, 1958, undated (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Culture II, 1958, undated (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Economics, 1944- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Exhibition New York World's Fair, 1939 (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Exhibition New York 1959 (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Foreign Affairs / Relations, 1951- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Jews, 1925- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Krokodil, 1947- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Labor Leadership (Report of visit by Prof Raffaele, Drexel College, Pennsylvania), 1960 (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): League of Nations, 1918 (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Manchuria, circa 1945 (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Manufacturers and Commerce, 1927- (Box 14)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Pamphlets and Publications, 1932-1967, undated (Box 15)
  - Russia (1923-USSR): Pamphlets and Publications I, 1940- (Box 15)
  - Russia (1923-USSR): Pamphlets and Publications II, 1940- (Box 15)
  - Russia (1923-USSR): Publication: National Geographic, 1914 (Box 15)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Religion, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Russia (1923- USSR): Soviet Man, circa 1950-, undated (Box 15)
  - Russia: Revolution 1917-1921, 1918-1967 (Box 15, Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Russian War Relief, 1944- (Box 15)
- S, 1902-2006; 6.25 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 4 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize flat box
  - S-1 (Senate Bill 1), 1975 (Box 15)
  - S. 1437 / H.R. 6869 (War Protestors), 1984, undated (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case I (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case II, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case III, 1911 (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case IV, undated (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case V (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case: Newspaper Clippings, 1927- (Box 15)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti Case: Pamphlets and Publications, 1927- (Box 15)
  - Schatman v. John Foster Dulles, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Schlesinger Case, 1949-1955 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Schneiderman v. United States, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Scrip Money, undated (Box 15)
  - Seabrook: Nuclear Power Plant, 1980- (Box 15)
  - Seattle Eight, undated (Box 15)
  - Segregation I, 1907-1955 (Box 15, Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Segregation II, 1907- (Box 15)
  - Selma (AL), 1965 (Box 15)
  - Seniority Clauses, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - September 11, 2001 (9/11), 2001-2003, undated (Box 15, Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Settlements, 1941- (Box 15)
  - Sharecroppers (MO), 1938 (Box 15)
  - Silent Slaughter -- Indonesia, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Silent Trial of Sacramento, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Single Tax, 1910- (Box 15)
  - Slavery, 1863-2012 (Box 15, Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Smith Act, 1949-1955 (Box 16, Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Smith Act: Newspaper Clippings, 1948- (Box 16)
  - Smith Act Trial, 1952 (Box 16)
  - Social Security, 1938-1999 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Social Welfare, 1940- (Box 16)
  - Socialism, 1903-2001 (Box 16, Box 46, Folder 13-14)
  - Socialism: Great Britain, 1916- (Box 16)
  - Socialism: United States, 1916- (Box 16)
  - Solar Energy, 1980, undated (Box 16)
  - Solidarity Day Sept. 19, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Songs: Union, Political, Folk I, 1888-2012 (Box 16, Box 47, Folder 1-4, Box 48, Folder 1-5, Box 49, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 186, Folder 8)
  - Songs: Union, Political, Folk II, 1923- (Box 16)
  - Songs: Union, Political, Folk III, 1923- (Box 16)
  - South Africa I, 1945-1977 (Box 16, Box 28, Folder 18, Box 46, Folder 16)
  - South Africa II, 1945- (Box 16)
  - Soweto, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Spain, 1946-1974 (Box 16, Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Spain: Civil War, 1936-1939, 1931-1972 (Box 16, Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Spanish Speakers, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Spanje Monument (Amsterdam), circa 1939 (Box 16)
  - Stamps (postage; commemorative), 1958- (Box 16)
  - Steel, 1959-1961 (Box 16)
  - Steelworkers, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Sterling Building Bombing, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Strategy Action Conference (Milwaukee, WI), Jun 1970 (Box 16)
  - Strikebreakers, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Allentown, PA, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Briggs Strike (Briggs Manufacturing Company, Detroit), 1933, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: British Dockers Strike, 1995-1997, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Brown and Sharp Manufacturing (RI): Machinists Union, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Coal Strikes, 1902, 1927 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Coal - Harlan County, KY, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: General Electric, 1969, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: General Strike (Great Britain) 1926, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Kohler Strike, 1957, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Leviton Strike, 1940, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Memphis Sanitation Workers Strike, 1968, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Minneapolis Teamsters Stirke of 1934, 1888-2012 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Oakland General Strike, 1947 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Olympia Theatre (Janitors and Doormen), 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Oshkosh WoodWorkers Strike, 1898, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Packinghouse Workers Strike, 1946 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Passaic Textile Strike, NJ of 1926 I, 1926-2006 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Passaic Textile Strike, NJ of 1926 II, 1926-2006 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Paterson Strike Pageant of 1913, 1913-1994 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Paterson Silk and Textile Workers Strike, 1924, 1927 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Paterson Silk and Textile Workers Strike, 1928 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Paterson Silk and Textile Workers Strike, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Paterson Silkworkers Strike, 1913, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Petrie-Red Robbin Strike Fund (Office workers union), 1935 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Phelps-Dodge Copper Strike, 1983-1985 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Philadelphia Transportation Company Strike, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Pullman Strike, undated (Box 16)
  - Strikes: San Francisco Strike, 1935 (Box 16)
  - Strikes: Seattle General Strike of 1919, 1961-1986 (Box 17)
  - Strikes: Shell Oil Company, Nov 1962 (Box 17)
  - Strikes: Sit-Down Strikes, 1937-1938 (Box 17)
  - Strikes: Steel Workers, 1992- (Box 17)
  - Strikes: Textile Strike - New Bedford, MA, 1928, undated (Box 17)
  - Strikes: Textile Strike - Lawrence, MA, 1912, 1912-1982 (Box 17)
  - Strikes: TWA Flight Engineers Strike, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Strip Mining (Southeastern United States; Council of the Southern Mountains), 1971 (Box 17)
  - Students, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Students, High School: Political Activity - General, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Students, High School: Political Activity (New York, NY), 1934-1950 (Box 17, Box Shared Tamiment 044, Folder 3)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Materials in box Shared Tamiment 044, folder 3 are fragile
  - Students: Political Activity, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (California), 1960s- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (California, Berkeley), 1964- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (City College of New York, NY), 1968- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University) I, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University) II, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University)- Anti-Strike Material, 1968- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University) 1968 Strike - Official University Material (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University) 1968 I, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Columbia University) 1968 II (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Cornell University), 1969 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity - General I, 1965- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity - General II, 1965- (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Harvard University), 1969 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Kent State), 1978 (Box 17)
  - Students: Political Activity (Long Island University), 1967 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (Louisiana-Southern University), 1972 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (Massachusetts Institute of Technology - MIT), 1970 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (New York Area), 1973 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (New York University) I, 1968- (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (New York University) II, 1968- (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (New York University) Anti-draft, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (San Francisco State College), 1969- (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (Stanford University) Student Strike Spring 1969 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (SUNY Stony Brook), 1972 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (University of Chicago), 1967 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (University of Connecticut), 1973 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (Washington State), 1962 (Box 18)
  - Students: Political Activity (Yale University), 1970 (Box 18)
  - Subversive Activities & Organizations -- U.S., 1955 (Box 18)
  - Sudeten (region of Czechoslovakia), 1938 (Box 18)
  - Suffrage, undated (Box 18)
  - Surveillance, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Sweatshops I, 2000-2006 (Box 18, Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Sweatshops II, 2000, undated (Box 18)
  - Sweden, 1938- (Box 18)
  - Sweden: Social Services and Employment I, undated (Box 18)
  - Sweden: Social Services and Employment II, undated (Box 18)
  - Switzerland, undated (Box 18)
  - Sydenham Hospital Closure, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Symbionese Liberation Army, undated (Box 18)
- T, 1882-2012; 2 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 shared box
  - Taff Vale Decision (Great Britain) formative case in UK labour law, 1900 (Box 19)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947- (Box 19)
  - Tanaka Document (Japan Imperialism), 1927 (Box 19)
  - Taxes, 1940-2003 (Box 19, Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Taylor Law, 1967- (Box 19)
  - Teaching, Freedom of (Academic Freedom), 1949- (Box 19)
  - Technology and Labor I, 1950s (Box 19)
  - Technology and Labor II, 1950s (Box 19)
  - Ten Hour Law: Illinois, 1909 (Box 19)
  - Ten Hour Movement: Labor Protests in Lowell, MA, circa 1986 (Box 19)
  - Tenants, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Tenement House Cigar Factories - Legislation (NY), 1882 (Box 19)
  - Terre Haute, Indiana: "Terre Haute's Shame: A Record of Graft and Swindle", 1915 (Box 19)
  - Terrorism, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Thailand, 1976- (Box 19)
  - Thällmann, Ernst -- Murder, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Theatre and Film, 1907-2012 (Box 19, Box 50, Folder 7-8)
  - Theatre & Socialism, 1982 (Box 19)
  - The "Third World", 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Thirty Hour Work Week, 1935, undated (Box 19)
  - Thompson v. McNamara, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Tibet, 1959, undated (Box 19, Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Time Study (production), 1916 (Box 19)
  - Tolpuddle Martyrs (Dorchester, England), 1945- (Box 19)
  - Tompkins Square Park Riot 1988, 2008 (Box 19)
  - Townsend Plan, 1935 (Box 19)
  - Trade Agreements (see also NAFTA), 1992- (Box 19)
  - Trade Unions: Great Britain, undated (Box 19)
  - Trade Unions (General), 1907, 1972, undated (Box 19)
  - Trade Unions: Background Materials on Various Countries, 1982, undated (Box 19)
  - Transportation, 1976-1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Transportation: New York Metropolitan Area - Subways, 1921 (Box 19)